yaoimangaonline.com 2019-05-28

# Privacy Policy (GDPR Compliant) - Yaoi Manga Online

Data Usage and Protection

1\. Introduction  
YaoiMangaOnline provides a web space where users and visitors can read manga/ doujinshi (Dj) online for free, purely for information purpose only, share impressions and join conversations. At YaoiMangaOnline the privacy and security of our members and visitors are of paramount importance. YaoiMangaOnline is committed to protecting the data you share with us. This privacy policy explains how YaoiMangaOnline processes information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify an individual (“Personal Data”) collected through use of its website and platform.  
For the purposes of this policy, YaoiMangaOnline defines the term “User” as an entity with which YaoiMangaOnline has an established relationship, and the term “Visitor” as an individual that visits our front-end website (for example www.YaoiMangaOnline.com).

Any information stored on YaoiMangaOnline’s platform is treated as confidential. All information is stored securely and is accessed by authorized personnel only. YaoiMangaOnline implements and maintains appropriate technical, security and organisational measures to protect Personal Data against unauthorized or unlawful processing and use, and against accidental loss, destruction, damage, theft or disclosure.

2\. Collection and use  
2.1 .General  
The following sections cover the specifics of each of the two groups from which data is collected: website Visitors and Users.

2.2 Website Visitors  
If you are a Visitor to our website only, and not a User of our platform, then this section is relevant for you.

By visiting this website, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Data as described herein. If you do not agree with the terms set out herein, please do not visit this website.  
YaoiMangaOnline may collect, record and analyze information of Visitors to its website. We may record your IP address and use cookies. YaoiMangaOnline may collect information in terms of pageview activity.  
YaoiMangaOnline gathers data about visits to the website, including numbers of Visitors and visits, Geo-location data, length of time spent on the site, pages clicked on or which page Visitors have come from.

2.2.1 Purpose of processing personal data  
YaoiMangaOnline uses the collected data to improve its website by analyzing how Visitors navigate its website.

2.2.2 Sharing personal data  
YaoiMangaOnline may also share such information with service vendors or contractors in order to provide a requested service or in order to analyze the Visitor behavior on its website.

2.2.3 Cookies  
Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a website to a Visitor’s hard disk. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. By continuing to visit the website, you agree to the placement of cookies on your device. If you choose not to accept our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience will be as fulfilling as it would otherwise be. We may also place cookies from third parties for functional and marketing purposes. The use of cookies is widespread and benefits the surfer.

2.2.4 Links to other sites  
Please be aware that while visiting our site, Visitors can follow links to other sites that are beyond our sphere of influence. YaoiMangaOnline is not responsible for the content or privacy policy of these other sites.

2.3 Users  
2.3.1. General  
In order to provide services to its Users, YaoiMangaOnline collects certain types of data from them. This section will describe how data is collected and used by YaoiMangaOnline as well as geographical differences that effect this policy. Data entered or transferred into YaoiMangaOnline by Users such as texts, questions, contacts, media files, etc., remains the property of the User and may not be shared with a third party by YaoiMangaOnline without express consent from the User.

2.3.2 Collection of User data  
During a User’s registration and later on YaoiMangaOnline’s platform, they provide information such as email address, username (it doesn’t have to be related in any way to your real name), location (it can be fictive, it doesn’t have to have any relation with your real physical location) and other optional data related to the User’s personal preferences. This information is used by YaoiMangaOnline to identify the User and provide them with support, services, subscriptions, mailings.

YaoiMangaOnline Users can at any time access and edit, update or delete their contact details by logging in with their username and password to YaoiMangaOnline’s platform. Users, at any time, can request the permanent deletion of their entire account. YaoiMangaOnline Users can choose the level of privacy of their profile (which by default isn’t crawled by bots or search engine spiders). Once a User logs into YaoiMangaOnline, they meet the definition of User in this policy. YaoiMangaOnline will not retain User data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.

2.3.3.1 Processing in the European Economic Area (EEA)  
For Users with accounts located in YaoiMangaOnline’s European Data Region, all processing of Personal Data is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the EU Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 (the Directive), and the implementations of the Directive in local legislation. From May 25th, 2018, the Directive and local legislation based on the Directive will be replaced by the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and YaoiMangaOnline’s processing will take place in accordance with the GDPR.

2.3.3.1.1 Controller  
YaoiMangaOnline processes Personal Data both as a Processor and as a Controller, as defined in the Directive and the GDPR:

The YaoiMangaOnline entity which you as a User entered an agreement with when using YaoiMangaOnline’s platform, will be the Controller for User data, as outlined above in “Collection of User data” section.  
YaoiMangaOnline adheres to the Directive of 1995 and the GDPR from May 25th, 2018. YaoiMangaOnline’s contract with its hosting provider ensures that all hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations. 

2.3.3.2 Processing in the United States Of America (US)  
YaoiMangaOnline has adopted reasonable physical, technical and organizational safeguards which substantially mirror the EU safeguards against accidental, unauthorized or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use or processing of the User’s data in YaoiMangaOnline’s possession. YaoiMangaOnline will promptly notify the User in the event of any known unauthorized access to, or use of, the User’s data.

YaoiMangaOnline’s contract with its hosting provider ensures that all hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations. YaoiMangaOnline’s policy is to protect and safeguard any personal information obtained by YaoiMangaOnline in accordance with United States state or federal laws governing the protection of personal information and data. Accordingly, YaoiMangaOnline adheres to practices and policies that aim to safeguard the data.

2.3.3.3 Processing in other regions  
YaoiMangaOnline has adopted reasonable physical, technical and organizational safeguards which substantially mirror the EU safeguards against accidental, unauthorized or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, disclosure, access, use or processing of the Users data in YaoiMangaOnline’s possession. YaoiMangaOnline will promptly notify the User in the event of any known unauthorized access to, or use of, the User’s data.  
YaoiMangaOnline’s contract with its hosting provider ensures that all hosting is performed in accordance with the highest security regulations. Accordingly, YaoiMangaOnline adheres to practices and policies that aim to safeguard the data.

3\. Retention and deletion  
YaoiMangaOnline will not retain data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. For Users data, YaoiMangaOnline staff will therefore have the responsibility to delete data when required. When a users’s account is terminated or expired, all Personal Data collected through the platform will be deleted, as required by applicable law.

4\. Acceptance of these Conditions  
We assume that all Visitors of our website and users of YaoiMangaOnline’s platform have carefully read this document and agree to its contents. If someone does not agree with this privacy policy, they should refrain from using our website and platform. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy as necessity dictates. Continued use of YaoiMangaOnline website and platform after having been informed of any such changes to these conditions implies acceptance of the revised privacy policy. This privacy policy is an integral part of YaoiMangaOnline’s terms of use.

5\. Our Legal Obligation to Disclose Personal Information  
We are permitted to disclose personal information when we have good reason to believe that this is legally required in case the user’s activity has harmed YaoiMangaOnline or other persons.

6\. YaoiMangaOnline’s Data Protection Officer  
YaoiMangaOnline has a “Data Protection Officer” who is responsible for matters relating to privacy and data protection. This Data Protection Officer can be reached at the following address:  
readmanga9@gmail.com

7\. For Further Information  
If you have any further questions regarding the data YaoiMangaOnline collects, or how we use it, then please feel free to contact us by email at: readmanga9@gmail.com
